https://www.terracon.com/privacy-policy/

Combined Shape
Created with Sketch.
Client Login
Search for:
PRIVACY POLICYTerracon Consultants, Inc. (“Terracon”) is sensitive to privacy issues concerning the use of information provided over the Internet. We understand the importance of protecting information that you may provide us through the use of this website. Please review the following General Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or concerns about this policy, please contact us.Privacy PolicyWhat information do we collect?We collect information from you when you respond to a survey or fill out a form. We also collect information about how you use our site by employing Google Analytics. Google Analytics anonymously tracks your movement within our site, and beyond with the use of cookies. Google has been tracking your web activity from the very first time you visited their search engine, saw one of their display ads, or visited another site that employs Google Analytics. They only share with us anonymous information about your time on our site. Your web activities beyond our site are not shared with us.How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps: www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/When sending a message through our contact form you may be asked for the following:Name,Company,E-mail address,Phone number,and/or mailing address.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To improve our website. (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)To improve customer service. (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To respond to your request for information.Do we honor “Do Not Track” browser requests?No. Our website does not support or comply with “Do Not Track” requests sent by your browser. If you do not want us to have any information about how to contact you, please do not fill out our form. If you do not want Google to track your use of our site please visit this page for Google’s information on opting out of tracking.Do third parties track your internet usage?Definitely, but we have no agreements enabling third parties to track any information you submit to us, nor do we willingly share your information with any other company.Do we use cookies?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe collect information you submit to us via our online forms. That information includes your name, email address, phone number, Company name and whatever comments you submit in the forms. We do not automatically harvest any personally identifiable information from your computer, nor do we contract any third parties for that purpose. We do not share the information you submit with third parties without your permission.Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). Our site is intended for use by business professionals seeking Search Engine Optimization or Internet Marketing services. We do not solicit any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Google Analytics DataMillions of websites, including Terracon.com use Google Analytics. We have configured our Google Analytics account to use Google’s Advertising features, including Google’s Demographics and Interest Reports as well as Google AdWords Remarketing features.Google analytics collects information about your visit to our site including:How you arrived at our website.How long you stay.What pages you visit.What kind of computer, browser, and operating system you are using.What page you exit our site.And much more.For more information about how Google uses the information they collect about you please visit their Privacy & Terms page. To opt out of Google’s tracking, please visit this page.What does Terracon do with the information Google records?The analytics data that Google collects, and shares with us, helps us better understand the kind of people that visit our sites and what they do when they visit. This information helps us make decisions for site structure, content, compatibility, and overall user experience.WE DO NOT AND CANNOT COLLECT ANY INFORMATION FROM GOOGLE ANALYTICS THAT COULD PERSONALLY IDENTIFY YOU.All activity on this site falls within the bounds of the Google Analytics Terms of Service.IndemnificationYou agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless Terracon, its affiliates and its and their respective owners, investors, contractors, officers, directors, members, managers, partners, shareholders, licensors, suppliers, customers, employees, agents, third-party advertisers, technology providers and service providers from and against any loss, damage, cost, or liability (including, reasonable attorneys’ fees) resulting from or relating in any way to any claim, demand, action or proceeding that arises out of the usage of our website. In plain English: You can’t sue us for anything related to the use of this website, including anything done by a third party via our website (ie., hacking, identity theft, etc.). Furthermore, you will defend us against any and all claims we might be a part of because of your use of our site. It’s highly unlikely anything bad will happen, but you agree that it’s not our fault if it does.CopyrightUnless specifically noted, the entirety of Terracon.com is copyright Terracon and not to be reproduced in whole or in part without explicit written permission. All copyright and trademark infringements will be prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law.Changes to our Privacy PolicyWe will decide if and when to update this policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. There will be no other notification so you are required to check back for updates.This policy was last modified on 7/30/2018Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below, visiting our site’s contact form, or the phone number provided in the footer of our website.Terracon Consultants, Inc. 10841 S. Ridgeview Road Olathe, KS 66061 United StatesImplied ConsentUsage of our site implies that you have read, understand, and agreed to all terms and statements made in this privacy policy.This policy applies to Terracon Consultants, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates.
Sign Up for our monthly newsletter
Services
Environmental
Facilities
Geotechnical
Materials
Markets
Agriculture
© 2020 Copyright Terracon. All rights reserved. | Privacy Policy
